<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Douglas Ramos, a top Real Estate Agent in North/Central Jersey, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://c21arcoaching.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://c21arcoaching.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 14:58:24 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 14:58:24 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>These 2 Strategies Can Help You Manage a Killer Database</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AO0NIDdpric?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you been managing your database lately?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many agents make the mistake of not paying enough attention to their past clients and building on those connections. Instead, they focus all of their energy on pursuing new clients. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t given much thought to how important it is to keep your present customers, remember this statistic that I mentioned in the previous video of this series: According to SourceLink.com, &lt;strong&gt;even a 5% increase in customer retention can increase your profitability by 75%.&lt;/strong&gt; Why not take care of the clients and customers who already know, like, and trust you? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Why not take care of the clients and customers who already know, like, and trust you?%20http://c21arcoaching.com/these-2-strategies-can-help-you-manage-a-killer-database.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Why not take care of the clients and customers who already know, like, and trust you?”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, here are a couple more strategies you can use to grow your business by creating and managing a killer database: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consider a “Five-a-Day&lt;/strong&gt;” contact program. It’s always easier to take small steps that will make a big impact. Start your day with a colorful piece of paper with five past clients, referral sources, or prospects. Make five touches and call every day, five days a week, and you’ll end each month with a healthy rotation through your database. The number of touches should be close to 100 calls. Your script doesn’t have to be complicated. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Send a note.&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re embarrassed about not staying in touch, think about sending a fun note and include a call to action to get any information about neighborhood news or any real estate activity in your area. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, we hope today’s message has been helpful, and be sure to look out for my next episode for even more great information. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 16:25:16 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://c21arcoaching.com/these-2-strategies-can-help-you-manage-a-killer-database.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://c21arcoaching.com/these-2-strategies-can-help-you-manage-a-killer-database.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Quick Q&amp;A With a Mortgage Professional</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nUZku5z7pmc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can a mortgage professional teach you about servicing your own customers and marketing your business from a mortgage professional? Today I’ve brought in loan originator Martin Witzburg for a quick interview so you can find out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For your convenience, I’ve provided timestamps of the video above so you can skip ahead to the section(s) that interest you the most: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:56—How Martin got into the mortgage industry&lt;br /&gt;1:48—Who Primary Residential Mortgage’s primary consumer is &lt;br /&gt;2:43—The No. 1 question customers ask (or should be asking) lenders&lt;br /&gt;4:16—The biggest problem customers typically run into (and what they can do to solve it)&lt;br /&gt;6:01—One of Marty’s client success stories &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any more questions for Marty, you can give him a call at &lt;strong&gt;(908) 294-0433&lt;/strong&gt;. As always, if you have any questions for me, don’t hesitate to call or email me. I’d love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 16:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://c21arcoaching.com/a-quick-qa-with-a-mortgage-professional.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://c21arcoaching.com/a-quick-qa-with-a-mortgage-professional.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Interview With New Horizon Mitigation</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dQlPKaitzwU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m here today with Frank Boccuzzi of New Horizon Mitigation. He’ll be sharing with us information about his business, its history, and what they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For your convenience, I’ve included timestamps of our conversation topics. Feel free to navigate to the section(s) you’re interested in viewing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;00:39— How long has New Horizon been in business?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;02:13— Who does the company market to?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;04:17— What is the biggest issue clients run into?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;05:50— Frank’s most interesting customer stories&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;07:26— Information about Frank’s upcoming Lunch-and-Learn event for short sales&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;08:37— How to get in contact with Frank&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to get in contact with Frank, give him a call at 908-838-9729, email &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#070;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#107;&amp;#064;&amp;#078;&amp;#072;&amp;#077;&amp;#105;&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#103;&amp;#097;&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;&amp;#070;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#107;&amp;#064;&amp;#078;&amp;#072;&amp;#077;&amp;#105;&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#103;&amp;#097;&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; or visit &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.NHMitigation.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.NHMitigation.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any real estate needs, have any questions, or need more information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 13:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://c21arcoaching.com/an-interview-with-new-horizon-mitigation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://c21arcoaching.com/an-interview-with-new-horizon-mitigation.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Reasons to Follow Up With Your Past Clients</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rapSA_wGw4k?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first installment into our three-part series on the importance of having a database. During this series, we’ll also cover 10 proven strategies to help you grow your real estate business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When talking to fellow real estate agents, it is always surprising to learn that many of them either don’t spend much time working on their database or don’t have one at all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many agents who are guilty of this may have a software program that houses a database, but they fail to utilize it. They don’t employ any sort of engagement strategy in order to nurture contacts and keep them liable, nor do they implement any sort of ongoing business growth strategies.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any successful business knows that your customers are your most important asset.&lt;/strong&gt; The process of buying or selling does not end at the closing. When nurtured and serviced after the sale, your client relationship opens the door to easier prospecting, endless referrals and repeat business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case you haven’t thought about why it’s important to keep your present customers, here’s a statistic that will convince you: SourceLink.com reports that even a “5% increase in customer retention can increase profitability by 75%”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=While the closing table may signal the end of a particular transaction, it shouldn’t represent the end of your relationship with a given client.%20http://c21arcoaching.com/5-reasons-to-follow-up-with-your-past-clients.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“While the closing table may signal the end of a particular transaction, it shouldn’t represent the end of your relationship with a given client.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this statistic alone isn’t enough to convince you of the value of staying in touch with clients who already know, like, and trust you, consider these five additional reasons you should do so: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Customers are your most important asset.&lt;/strong&gt; While the closing table may signal the end of a particular transaction, it shouldn’t represent the end of your relationship with a given client. Think of closing, instead, as a gateway to future business. To maintain client relationships, though, you will need a system that can deliver consistent, systematic contact features to help keep your brand and name in front of your database. There are countless real estate software programs that can help organize your contacts before, during, and long after a transaction has closed. Explore your options to see which platform works best for your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. It’s easier to sell to existing customers.&lt;/strong&gt; According to MarketingMetrics.com, you have a 60% chance of selling to an existing customer, but a mere 5% to 20% chance of successfully selling to a new one. Therefore, you should never neglect your past clients when nurturing contacts.  Take at least one day per week to work on your database. Start from the current year and work backward to organize, review, and upload customer information so you can begin the process of contacting, nurturing, and informing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. You can save five times more on marketing.&lt;/strong&gt; Nurturing existing relationships is significantly less expensive than developing new ones; Forrester Research reports that, in today’s market, it costs five times more to acquire a customer than it does to keep current ones. Using a client relationship management system (CRM) is critical if you hope to continually nurture and maintain strong relationships with past clients. Ideally, the relationships you make with clients should be lifelong ones. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. There are plenty of easy, inexpensive ways to build an effective database.&lt;/strong&gt; Despite this, many agents are so busy working with current prospects that they can’t keep up with prospecting for new customers. If your present website isn’t working 24/7, you will lose the prospecting and marketing edge. Even something as simple as having a website that uses effective lead capture features coupled with ongoing communication and marketing messaging can help you stay connected with your prospects during the incubation process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Old customers are a great source of business.&lt;/strong&gt; Following up with past clients will remind them to think of you when they or someone they know needs your services in the future. A good old-fashioned phone call and handwritten thank-you note can, and often will, do the trick. Once you’ve reignited the relationship, be ready to continue the engagement with consistent communication touches to keep the connection warm. Set up a marketing calendar and schedule recurring follow-up engagements at least once a month. Offering valuable information through market reports, incentivizing engagement with gift card giveaways, or hosting seasonal competitions or small social events will help you stay top-of-mind with past clients. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope today’s message has been helpful. If it has, be sure to look out for our next two episodes for even more great information. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 16:28:19 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://c21arcoaching.com/5-reasons-to-follow-up-with-your-past-clients.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://c21arcoaching.com/5-reasons-to-follow-up-with-your-past-clients.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Earn Your Clients’ Trust</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CnVfOmnO11c?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A trusting relationship is important, especially when it comes to real estate. Today we’ll be discussing how you can build trust with your clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In real estate, important things can happen quickly, so the relationships between an agent and their clients must be built on trust. &lt;strong&gt;Trust building begins immediately in the first interaction&lt;/strong&gt;—ensuring you’re all on the same team allows you to work together to accomplish real estate goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The relationship between an agent and their client must be built on trust.%20http://c21arcoaching.com/how-to-earn-your-clients-trust.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The relationship between an agent and their client must be built on trust.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So, how can we get clients who we’ve just met to trust us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Referrals from friends and family do wonders. You’ll have a better chance of starting off on the right foot, but the first impression you make is still important. Also, professionals with a reputation for being ethical can earn trust more easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The three R’s of respect are vital elements of earning trust:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Recognition.&lt;/strong&gt; When an agent doesn’t recognize the value in a prospective client, the client won’t recognize the value in the agent, either. Make it clearly evident you are aware of the value they carry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Reliability.&lt;/strong&gt; You and your team members must be predictable, reliable, and follow through with clients.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Resourcefulness.&lt;/strong&gt; Prospective clients want to find professionals who put clients’ interests first. You must do what it takes to get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need more information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 15:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://c21arcoaching.com/how-to-earn-your-clients-trust.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://c21arcoaching.com/how-to-earn-your-clients-trust.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To My Blog!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about becoming involved in real estate professionally, we are looking to expand our Century 21 Alliance Realty team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you’re a licensed real estate agent who wants to jump-start your career or you want to join a team with the necessary tools to enhance your performance, I invite you to apply for a position with our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We shine because we provide strong guidance and success training to our team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going forward, our team is going to send out two monthly videos that will include market updates, community information, tips to improve your business, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check back because content will be coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m excited to keep you informed on how to promote and begin your real estate career!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://c21arcoaching.com/welcome-to-my-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://c21arcoaching.com/welcome-to-my-blog.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
